<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2015, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 16:22:58 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 16:22:58 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>Apple Watch Available in Nine Countries on April 24</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/watch/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that Apple Watch will be available April 24 to customers in Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, the UK, and the U.S. Apple Watch brings an entirely new way to receive information at a glance and interact with the world through third-party apps designed specifically for the wrist. “Apple Watch begins a new chapter in the way we relate to technology and we think our customers are going to love it,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We can’t wait for people to start wearing Apple Watch to easily access information that matters, to interact with the world, and to live a better day by being more aware of their daily activity than ever before.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:11:20 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Unveils All-New MacBook</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/macbook/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled the all-new MacBook, a thinner and lighter line of notebooks available in gold, silver, and space gray aluminum finishes. MacBook features a 12-inch Retina display; a full-size keyboard; the all-new Force Touch trackpad; a compact USB-C port for data transfer, video out, and charging in a single connector; and a new battery designed to deliver all-day life. “Apple has reinvented the notebook with the new MacBook, and at just 2 pounds and 13.1 millimeters, it’s the thinnest and lightest Mac ever,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “Every component of the MacBook reveals a new innovation. From its fanless design, ultrathin Retina display, and full-size keyboard that’s 34 percent thinner, to its all-new Force Touch trackpad, versatile USB-C port, and breakthrough terraced battery design, the new MacBook is the future of the notebook.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:09:51 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Updates 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina Display and MacBook Air</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/03/09Apple-Updates-13-inch-MacBook-Pro-with-Retina-Display-MacBook-Air.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated the 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display and the 11-inch and 13-inch MacBook Air. “Today, the popular 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display, 11-inch MacBook Air and 13-inch MacBook Air all received significant upgrades,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “The 13-inch MacBook Pro has been updated with the latest processors, more powerful graphics, faster flash, longer battery life, and the all-new Force Touch trackpad. We’re also bringing the latest processors and graphics and faster Thunderbolt 2 to the 11-inch and 13-inch MacBook Air, as well as up to two times faster flash to the 13-inch MacBook Air.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:08:29 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces ResearchKit, Giving Medical Researchers New Tools</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/researchkit/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced ResearchKit, an open-source software framework designed for medical and health research that can help doctors and scientists gather data more frequently and more accurately from participants using iPhone apps. World-class research institutions have already developed apps with ResearchKit for studies on asthma, breast cancer, cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and Parkinson’s disease. “iOS apps already help millions of customers track and improve their health. With hundreds of millions of iPhones in use around the world, we saw an opportunity for Apple to have an even greater impact by empowering people to participate in and contribute to medical research,” said Jeff Williams, Apple’s senior vice president of Operations. “ResearchKit gives the scientific community access to a diverse, global population and more ways to collect data than ever before.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:07:41 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HBO NOW Premiering in April; Subscription Available to Apple Customers </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/03/09HBO-NOW-Premiering-in-April.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple and HBO today announced HBO NOW is premiering next month, making an HBO subscription available directly to Apple customers for the first time ever. iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, and Apple TV users can purchase HBO NOW directly in-app as a standalone service to watch HBO’s original programming, Hollywood hit movies, documentaries, sports, and comedy specials for $14.99 a month. “HBO NOW offers a new generation of HBO fans many of the best TV programs in the world without a cable or satellite subscription,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “Now, with the same simplicity as buying an app, customers can subscribe to HBO NOW and instantly start viewing their favorite HBO programs as they air — this is huge.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:00:26 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>A New Take on Feature Film Post-Production</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/final-cut-pro/in-action/focus/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>After researching several workflows, directors John Requa and Glenn Ficarra decided to edit “Focus” — a major new Warner Bros. film starring Will Smith — entirely in Final Cut Pro X. The results were even better than they’d expected. Final Cut Pro X helped them deliver the movie on time and under budget, and it played and looked just as they’d envisioned it. “I’ve cut on all the other systems, and I can easily say I’m three times faster on Final Cut Pro X,” says Ficarra.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 12:34:44 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Record First Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/01/27Apple-Reports-Record-First-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2015 first quarter ended December 27, 2014. The company posted record quarterly revenue of $74.6 billion and record quarterly net profit of $18 billion, or $3.06 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $57.6 billion and net profit of $13.1 billion, or $2.07 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 39.9 percent compared to 37.9 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 65 percent of the quarter’s revenue. The results were fueled by all-time record revenue from iPhone and Mac sales as well as record performance of the App Store. iPhone unit sales of 74.5 million also set a new record. “We’d like to thank our customers for an incredible quarter, which saw demand for Apple products soar to an all-time high,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “Our revenue grew 30 percent over last year to $74.6 billion, and the execution by our teams to achieve these results was simply phenomenal.” </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 15:22:51 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title> App Store Rings in 2015 with New Records</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/01/08App-Store-Rings-in-2015-with-New-Records.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>The first week of January set a new record for billings from the App Store. Apple customers worldwide spent nearly half a billion dollars on apps and in-app purchases, and New Year’s Day 2015 marked the single biggest day ever in App Store sales history. These milestones follow a breakthrough 2014, in which billings rose 50 percent and apps generated over $10 billion in revenue for developers. “This year is off to a tremendous start after a record-breaking year for the App Store and our developer community,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “We’re so proud of the creativity and innovation developers bring to the apps they create for iOS users and that the developer community has now earned over $25 billion.” </description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 12:06:36 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Developers Start Designing Apps for Apple Watch</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2014/11/18Developers-Start-Designing-Apps-for-Apple-Watch.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced the availability of WatchKit, software that gives developers a set of tools to easily create experiences designed specifically for Apple Watch. Developers can now begin developing WatchKit apps before the watch becomes available. “Apple Watch is our most personal device ever, and WatchKit provides the incredible iOS developer community with the tools they need to create exciting new experiences right on your wrist,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “With the iOS 8.2 beta SDK, developers can now start using WatchKit to create breakthrough new apps, Glances, and actionable notifications designed for the innovative Apple Watch interface and work with new technologies such as Force Touch, Digital Crown, and Taptic Engine.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 14:06:24 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Fourth-Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2014/10/20Apple-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2014 fourth quarter ended September 27, 2014. The company posted quarterly revenue of $42.1 billion and quarterly net profit of $8.5 billion, or $1.42 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $37.5 billion and net profit of $7.5 billion, or $1.18 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 38 percent compared to 37 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 60 percent of the quarter’s revenue. Apple’s board of directors has declared a cash dividend of $.47 per share of the company’s common stock. The dividend is payable on November 13, 2014, to shareholders of record as of the close of business on November 10, 2014. “Our fiscal 2014 was one for the record books, including the biggest iPhone launch ever with iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “With amazing innovations in our new iPhones, iPads, and Macs, as well as iOS 8 and OS X Yosemite, we are heading into the holidays with Apple’s strongest product lineup ever. We are also incredibly excited about Apple Watch and other great products and services in the pipeline for 2015.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 14:22:13 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces iPad Air 2 and iPad mini 3</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has introduced iPad Air 2, the thinnest and most powerful iPad ever. The new iPad features an improved Retina display for enhanced contrast and richer, more vibrant colors, and better cameras for taking stunning photos and videos. Available in gold, silver, and space gray, iPad Air 2 and the new iPad mini 3 offer Touch ID and — in the U.S. — Apple Pay. “iPad is a magical piece of glass that runs more than 675,000 apps specifically designed for it, and is thin and light enough that you can comfortably hold it all day; the new iPad Air 2 is packed with amazing new innovations, weighs less than a pound, and at just 6.1 mm is the thinnest tablet in the world,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “iPad Air 2 has a new Retina display with anti-reflective coating, second generation 64-bit A8X chip, all-new iSight and FaceTime HD cameras, faster Wi-Fi and LTE wireless, and includes the revolutionary Touch ID fingerprint identity sensor.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 14:04:21 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Pay Set to Transform Mobile Payments Starting October 20</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/apple-pay/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that customers can start making payments with the touch of a finger on October 20, when Apple Pay becomes available in the U.S. Apple Pay offers an easy, secure, and private way to pay using Touch ID on iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in stores and within apps. Users of the just-announced iPad Air 2 and iPad mini 3 will be able to use Touch ID on their devices for Apple Pay within apps. The new service will be enabled by a free software update to iOS 8. “Our team has worked incredibly hard to make Apple Pay private and secure, with the simplicity of a single touch of your finger,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “The reaction to Apple Pay has been amazing. We continue to add more Apple Pay-ready banks, credit card companies, and merchants, and think our users will love paying with Apple Pay.”
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 13:59:51 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>OS X Yosemite Now Available as a Free Upgrade</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/osx/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that OS X Yosemite, the latest major release of the world’s most advanced desktop operating system, is now available as a free upgrade for Mac users from the Mac App Store. Yosemite delivers a fresh, modern look and introduces Continuity features that make it easy to hand off activities between Mac and iOS devices and even make and receive iPhone calls from your Mac. Yosemite also includes a new Today view, a redesigned Spotlight, and updated versions of Safari, Mail, Messages, and iTunes. “OS X Yosemite is the most advanced version of OS X we’ve ever built, with a brand new design, amazing Continuity features, and powerful versions of the apps you use every day,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering. “OS X Yosemite ushers in the future of computing, where your Apple devices all work together seamlessly and magically. It’s something only Apple can do, and it’s available today.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 13:59:06 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces 27-inch iMac with Retina 5K Display</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/imac-with-retina/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has unveiled the 27-inch iMac with Retina 5K display, featuring the world’s highest-resolution display — with 14.7 million pixels. At this resolution, text appears sharper than ever, videos are more lifelike, and you can see new levels of detail in photos. “Thirty years after the first Mac changed the world, the new iMac with Retina 5K display running OS X Yosemite is the most insanely great Mac we have ever made,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “With a breathtaking 14.7-million-pixel display, faster CPU and graphics, Fusion Drive, and Thunderbolt 2, it’s the most beautiful and powerful iMac ever.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 13:47:49 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Updates Mac mini</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/mac-mini/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated Mac mini with the latest technologies and a new lower starting price, making Apple’s most affordable Mac an even better value. Mac mini now features fourth-generation Intel Core processors, faster integrated graphics, 802.11ac Wi-Fi, and Thunderbolt 2. “People love Mac mini. It’s a great first Mac or addition to your home network, and the new Mac mini is a nice upgrade packed into an incredibly compact design,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “With the latest CPU and graphics, faster Wi-Fi, two Thunderbolt 2 ports, OS X Yosemite, and starting at just $499, the new Mac mini is the best value ever.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 13:46:41 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus Available in China on October 17</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2014/09/30iPhone-6-iPhone-6-Plus-Available-in-China-on-Friday-October-17.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus will be available in China beginning October 17 from the Apple Online Store, Apple’s retail stores, and an expansive network of retail stores through all three major carriers and Apple Authorized Resellers. Customers can pre-order iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus from the Apple Online Store starting October 10. Beginning October 14, customers can reserve the new iPhones for in-store pick-up starting October 17. “We are thrilled to bring iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus to our customers in China on all three carriers at launch,” said Apple’s CEO Tim Cook. “With support for TD-LTE and FDD-LTE, iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus customers will have access to high-speed mobile networks from China Mobile, China Telecom, and China Unicom for an incredible experience.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 15:33:57 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>First Weekend iPhone Sales Top 10 Million, Set New Record</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone-6/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has sold over 10 million new iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus models, a new record, just three days after the launch on September 19. The iPhones are available in the US, Australia, Canada, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, Puerto Rico, Singapore, and the UK and will be available in more than 20 additional countries on September 26. The new phones will be available in 115 countries by the end of the year. “Sales for iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus exceeded our expectations for the launch weekend, and we couldn’t be happier,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We would like to thank all of our customers for making this our best launch ever, shattering all previous sell-through records by a large margin. While our team managed the manufacturing ramp better than ever before, we could have sold many more iPhones with greater supply and we are working hard to fill orders as quickly as possible.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 10:31:42 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Unveils Apple Watch — Apple’s Most Personal Device Ever</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/watch/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has unveiled Apple Watch — its most personal device ever — featuring revolutionary new technologies and a pioneering user interface with a beautiful design that honors the rich tradition of precision watchmaking. Apple Watch introduces a specially designed and engineered Digital Crown that provides an innovative way to scroll, zoom, and navigate. Apple Watch will enable you to communicate in new ways right from your wrist and will include comprehensive health and fitness apps. The watch comes in three distinct collections — Apple Watch, Apple Watch Sport, and Apple Watch Edition — available in two different sizes. “Apple introduced the world to several category-defining products, the Mac, iPod, iPhone, and iPad,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “And once again Apple is poised to captivate the world with a revolutionary product that can enrich people’s lives. It’s the most personal product we’ve ever made.” Apple Watch will be available in early 2015.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 14:43:39 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus — the Biggest Advancements in iPhone History</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone-6/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus, the biggest advancements in iPhone history, featuring two new models with stunning 4.7-inch and 5.5-inch Retina HD displays, and packed with innovative technologies in an all-new dramatically thin and seamless design. Both phones include the Apple-designed A8 chip with second generation 64-bit desktop-class architecture, advanced iSight and FaceTime HD cameras, ultrafast wireless technologies, iOS 8, and Apple Pay. “iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are the biggest advancements in iPhone history,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “The iPhone is the most loved smartphone in the world with the highest customer satisfaction in the industry and we are making it much better in every way. Only Apple can combine the best hardware, software, and services at this unprecedented level and we think customers are going to love it.” The new iPhones will be available September 19, and customers can pre-order them beginning September 12. </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 14:43:03 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces Apple Pay</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/apple-pay/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced Apple Pay, a new category of service that will transform mobile payments with an easy, secure, and private way to pay. Apple Pay works with iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus through a groundbreaking NFC antenna design, a dedicated chip called the Secure Element, and the security and convenience of Touch ID. Apple Pay is easy to set up, so hundreds of millions of users can simply add their credit or debit card on file from their iTunes Store account. Apple Pay will also work with the newly announced Apple Watch, extending Apple Pay to over 200 million owners of iPhone 5, iPhone 5c, and iPhone 5s worldwide. “Security and privacy is at the core of Apple Pay. When you’re using Apple Pay in a store, restaurant or other merchant, cashiers will no longer see your name, credit card number, or security code, helping to reduce the potential for fraud,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “Apple doesn’t collect your purchase history, so we don’t know what you bought, where you bought it, or how much you paid for it. And if your iPhone is lost or stolen, you can use Find My iPhone to quickly suspend payments from that device.” Apple Pay will be available in the U.S. for iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus as a free update to iOS 8 starting in October.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 14:41:13 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>